我叫巴里·艾伦 我是这个世界上最快的人
My name is Barry Allen, and I am the fastest man alive.
我还小的时候 目睹母亲
When I was a child, I saw my mother killed
死于一场奇异事件
by something impossible.
跑啊 巴里 快跑
Run, Barry. Run.
我的父亲蒙冤入狱
My father went to prison for her murder.
我在一场意外中获得了特异能力
Then an accident made me the impossible.
外人眼里 我只是个普普通通的法医
To the outside world, I'm an ordinary forensics scientist,
但私下里 我凭借闪电般的速度
but secretly, I use my speed
来打击罪犯 寻找我的同类
to fight crime and find others like me.
总有一天 我会找出杀我母亲的凶手
And one day, I'll find who killed my mother.
-妈妈 -为我父亲洗清冤屈
- Mom. - And get justice for my father.
我是闪电侠
I am The Flash.
《闪电侠》前情提要
Previously, on The Flash...
你以为你是谁
Who do you think you are?
我们说好了 用我的特异能力来行善
This is what we talked about, using my speed to do good.
我们说的是 由你来帮助我们克制其他超能力者
We talked about you helping us contain other meta-humans.
上了那么多记者培训课之后 我开了一个博客
After all of these journalism classes, I started a blog.
我觉得你上的是记者培训课
I thought you were taking journalism,
而不是科幻小说课
not science fiction writing.
从我遇见你那天开始
Ever since I have known you,
你就一直相信不可能的事
you have believed in the impossible.
如果你所说的母亲死亡真相 都是真的怎么办
What if you were right about the night that your mom died?
一定有人在默默地行善救人
Something out there is saving people.
很快就能见面了 巴里
See you soon, Barry.
你会经常思考这个问题吗
How often do you think about
为什么你的朋友会闯进你的生活
why your friends came into your life?
是随机事件 预谋好的 还是两者都有一点
Was it random, by design, or maybe a little of both?
好棒
Nice.
抛开这些原因 有些朋友你心里知道
Regardless of the reason, some friends you just know
会陪你走过一段时光
are gonna be by your side for a while.
至于其他朋友嘛 就不太确定了
Others, you're not so sure.
然后就会有某一位朋友 你真心希望
And then there's that one friend who, well, you hope,
能与之一直走下去
someday becomes something more.
可是朋友毕竟还只是朋友
But friend will have to do for now.
这也很不错
And that's okay.
也许吧
I guess.
我很高兴你也请了凯特琳和思科
I'm glad you invited Caitlin and Cisco.
他们都很酷 是么
They're cool, right?
他们简直拯救了你的生活 巴里
They saved your life, Barry.
所以对我来说 他们是我见过最酷的人
That makes them the coolest people I've ever met.
你们几个能做朋友真好
It's nice that you guys became friends.
致我们的朋友们 老朋友和新朋友
To friends, old and new.
呼 该我上啦
Ooh. I'm up.
祝我好运吧
Wish me luck.
我会击垮你的
I'm going to destroy you.
别太嚣张哦 韦斯特
Don't get cocky, West.
伙计们 我遇到问题了
Guys? I have a problem.
有这样一个男人存在 我们都会有问题
We all do when guys like him exist.
是啊 他太性感了
Yeah, he's so hot.
我是说 从遗传学角度讲
Uh, I mean, genetically speaking.
因为我是个遗传学家 当然
Because I'm a geneticist, of course.
天呐 我的语气像费莉希蒂吗
Oh, my God, do I sound like Felicity?
我说的不是埃迪
I'm not talking about Eddie.
我说的是这个
I'm talking about this.
我什么感觉都没有
I can't feel anything.
是啊 喝太多之后都会这样的吧
Yeah, that's usually what happens when you drink too much.
不是啦 我是说酒精对我不起作用
No, the alcohol is not affecting me.
我是说我真的没有感觉
I mean I literally feel nothing.
是你代谢过盛的原因 我要采点你的血样
It's your hyper-metabolism. I need a sample.
我去弄点酒来
I'll get more shots.
我发誓我这里有个真空采血管的
I swear, I had a Vacutainer here.
等等 你包里还随身带着采血器
Wait, you carry a blood collection kit in your purse?
人都有爱好的吧
You have your hobbies.
-14楼安全 -收到
- 14th floor is secure. - Roger that.
等等 有情况
Hold off on that check.
封锁全大楼
Lock down the building!
不许动
Hold it!
别靠近我
Don't come near me.
我要你跟我过来 快
You need to come with me. Come on.
趴下
Get down!
-还是没感觉 -我醉不了
- Still nothing? - I can't get drunk.
我才二十五岁呀
I mean, I'm only 25,
烂醉如泥的日子一去不复返了
and my drinking days are already over.
来吧 艾伦 轮到你啦
Come on, Allen. You're up.
第八大街和帕斯街交界处发生了爆炸
There was a bombing on 8th and pass.
-我得走了 亲爱的 -好
- I got to go, babe. - Okay.
抱歉了 伙计们
Sorry, guys.
我要去咖啡厅上早班了
I've got an early shift at Jitters.
巴里 咱们明天见
Barry, we'll catch up tomorrow.
总之有点晚了 所以我
It's getting late, anyway, so I'm just gonna...
救命 救命
Help! Help!
来救救我
Somebody!
伙计们 大楼上有个擦窗工 他要摔下来了
Guys, there's a window washer, and he's gonna fall.
别去抓他
Don't try and catch him.
你的力量不够
You don't have super strength.
好吧 那这周围有床铺店吗
Well, is there, like, a bed store near here?
我去弄一堆床垫叠在下面怎么样
What if I get a bunch of mattresses and stack them?
巴里 这可不是在动画片里
Barry, this isn't a roadrunner cartoon.
救命
Help! Help!
我要跑多快 才能跑上大楼侧面不掉下来
How fast would I need to go to run up the side of a building?
你想上多高
How far up do you need to go?
快啊 救命啊
Hurry, somebody!
不知道啊 50米 差不多吧
I don't know. 50 meters, give or take.
32.56
32.56...
-伙计们 速度啊 -救命
- Guys, hurry! - Help!
能多快就多快吧 你会没事的
Just run really fast and you'll be fine.
不过你下来的时候还是要保持速度 不然
But you need to maintain your velocity on the way down, or...
不然咋样
Or what?
啪嗒
Splat.
-好吧 -救命
- Great. - Help!
没事的 没事的 没事的
All right. All right, all right, all right.
我来也
Here goes.
闪电侠
第一季 第五集
视频字幕由 SSK字幕组 制作发布
字幕只供学习 请勿做任何商业行为
敬请关注新浪微博@SSK字幕组
合作贴吧：美剧闪电侠吧
翻译：香蕉奶昔 金刚妹 Bunny Windy Jophy Rubens
巴里 有什么发现吗
Barry? What do you got?
通常情况下放炸弹的人都会留下他们的印记
Bombers typically have their own unique signatures.
弯曲的引线 碎片什么的
Crimped wires, fragmentation.
校对：Bunny 香蕉奶昔 爱吃
我以前研究过这种精密程度的炸弹
The level of sophistication is telling once I've analyzed it.
我一看到炸弹 一般我都能找到线索
You show me a bomb, I can usually find a clue in it.
还有个但是 是吧
It sounds like there's a but Coming.
但是 这里没有任何氧化剂的迹象
Yeah, I haven't found any sign of an oxidizing agent.
时轴：络睿   压制：hhjie   总监：络睿 Bunny
感觉这地板平白无故地就炸了
It's as if the floor just blew itself up.
没有东西会平白无故地炸开来
Things don't just blow up.
保安说是一个红头发的女的扔的炸弹
Security guard said our bomber was a woman, red hair.
肯定有人对摄像头动了手脚
Must've cut the security camera's feed.
合作贴吧：美剧闪电侠吧
我们没有录像 但兴许能发现点其他的东西
There's no footage, but there might be something else.
门把被小型炸药炸掉了
Some kind of small charge blasted the doorknob off.
有发现丢失了什么吗
Any idea what's missing?
我猜应该是有文件被拿走了
My guess is one of these files.
不过得花上几天来找出是哪一份
It's gonna take days to figure out which one.
还是让巴里来做吧
Let's let Barry do his thing.
- 怎么了 - 不知道
- What's going on? - I have no idea.
但那架势 感觉这地方就是他的一样
But they came in here like they own the place.
和辛格谈了半个小时了
Been talking to Singh for the last half hour.
肯定没什么好事
This can't be good.
艾灵将军 这位是韦斯特探长
General Eiling, this is detective West.
你好
Detective.
这是什么情况
What's this all about?
军方将接管这起爆炸事件调查
The army's taking over the bombing investigation.
把你知道的都告诉我
I'll need everything you have.
包括物证 照片 目击者采访
Physical evidence, photographs, witness interviews,
还有你的个人案件记录
and all your personal notes.
我干这行都20年了
I've been on the job nearly 20 years
从来没遇到过军方要调查平民案件的
and never heard of the army investigating anything civilian.
这不是平民案件 她是我们的人
Well, it's not civilian. She's one of ours.
我们会把所有的资料都给你的
We'll send over everything we got.
万分感谢
Very kind of you.
我们现在就要接手
I think we'll take it now, though.
把东西给他们吧 乔
Give them what they want, Joe.
你也听到了 乔 把东西给我
You heard him, Joe. Give me what I want.
怎么了
Hey, what's going on?
艾灵将军从我们这儿接管了爆炸案件
General Eiling is relieving us from the bombing case.
把相关的资料都给他们
Give these men everything that's relevant.
好吧
Sure thing, yeah.
你和科技之星实验室的人
You and a few civilians from S.T.A.R. Labs
估计也想调查一下
might want to check into that.
我想也是
I think we might.
乔 我能和你聊一下吗
Can I talk to you for a minute, Joe?
和艾瑞斯有关
It's about Iris.
嘿 爸 你提早回来啦
Hey, dad. You're home early.
中城警署
你昨晚在爆炸案现场干什么
What were you doing at the bomb site last night?
别想抵赖 佛科维奇警官都看到你了
Don't deny you were there. Officer Vukuvich saw you.
很 难说啦
It's... Complicated.
你不能因为担心埃迪
You can't be coming to every crime scene
就跑去每个犯罪现场
because you're worried about Eddie.
他不是小孩子了 艾瑞斯
He's a big boy, Iris.
我不是去看埃迪的
I didn't go there to see Eddie.
我是去找红色踪迹的
I went there to see the streak.
红色踪迹 嗯 为什么
The streak. Hmm, why is that?
写博客
My blog.
我在收集网上关于红色踪迹
I've been collecting Internet posts
的信息 我在写相关的文章
about the streak sightings, and writing about them.
宝贝 根本没有什么红色踪迹
Baby, there's no streak.
不 有的
Yes, there is.
我昨晚看到他了 爸 他就站在我面前
I saw him last night, dad. I looked right at him.
肯定有神奇的事在中城上演
Something incredible is happening in Central City.
而我要把它写出来
And I am gonna write about it.
如果你不介意 我得干活了
Now, if you'll excuse me, I have to get to work.
要把那些一般稿酬不高的超自然事件都写到博客上
Blogging about supernatural events doesn't really pay well.
对于整个爆炸事件你就只拿到了一个文件号
A va file number is all the info you have on the bomber?
中城警局已经不能插手这个案子了
C.C.P.D's been ordered off the case.
谁权力那么大
Well, who has the power to do that?
军方 将军什么的
The army. Some general.
叫艾灵什么的吧
His name was Eiling, I think.
韦德·艾灵将军
General Wade Eiling.
- 你认识他 - 是的
- You know him? - Yeah, I know him.
大约十年前 韦德·艾灵将军
About ten years ago, general Wade Eiling
和科技之星实验室订约
contracted S.T.A.R. Labs to develop
发展军用的升级基因疗法
enhanced gene therapies for soldiers.
我对其中潜在的
I was interested in the potential
平民受惠很感兴趣
medical benefits for civilians.
艾灵将军一心想着
General Eiling really wanted to develop
发展读心能力 用以审讯
mind reading capabilities for interrogation purposes.
但当我近距离接触他的技术的时候
I stopped the study when I saw his techniques up close,
我们分道扬镳了 闹得也很不愉快
but our split was less than amicable.
他把我收集到的所有证据都拿走了
He took all the evidence I collected on the bombing.
除了这个文件夹
Everything but the folder.
算我们走运 这份文件
Well... Lucky for us, the va finally
有相关记录 并且已经数字化
joined the new millennium and digitized their records.
里面有很多记录
A lot of redacted info.
我们找的这个女的叫贝蒂·圣苏西
But our girl's name is Bette Sans Souci,
军队里的爆炸处理专家
an EOD specialist for the army.
- 爆炸处理 - 也就是炸弹啦
- EOD? - Bombs.
有地址吗
Is there an address?
等等 找到了
Hold on. Here, we go.
以防万一 是孤身一人
One person in case of emergency.
卡梅伦·斯科特 英格尔伍德
Cameron Scott. Inglewood.
贝蒂·圣苏西吗
Bette Sans Souci?
跟我走一趟
I need you to come with me.
别碰我
Don't touch me.
脱了你这身装束
Get whatever you're wearing off of you.
快点
Hurry.
巴里
Barry?
你能听到我说话吗 巴里
Can you hear me? Barry?
一定会有个解释他没有回应的
There must be a perfectly reasonable explanation
完美理由
for why he's not answering.
巴里
Barry?
额
Uh...
别问了
Don't ask.
我要问 我的套装呢
I'm gonna ask. Where's my suit?
它 没了
It's... gone.
什么叫 没了
What do you mean, it's gone?
你对我的套装做了些什么
What did you do with my suit?
它爆炸了 伙计
It blew up, dude.
我好不容易脱下来了 在它
I managed to get out of it before it went,
-嘣 之前 -我的套装 嘣 了
- kaboom.- My suit went Kaboom?
关于贝蒂·圣苏西的有意思的是
Fun fact about Bette Sans Souci.
她没有携带炸弹
She's not carrying bombs.
她碰了套装上的的徽章
She touched the emblem on the suit
就把它变成了炸弹
and turned it into a bomb.
她是个超能力者
She's a meta-human.
具有通过触碰引发自燃
With the ability to cause spontaneous combustion
的能力
upon tactile contact.
-她炸了我的套装 -你不是还有三件吗
- She blew up my suit. - You have, like, three more.
好吧 我只有两件 而且我超爱那一件
Okay, I have two. And I loved that one.
好吧 我们还了解她的什么信息
All right, what else do we know about her?
噢 我不知道啊 比如她是个超级恶魔
Oh, I don't know. She's pure evil.
我们要找到这个女的
We're gonna find this girl
然后把她塞到管道监狱里
and send her butt into the pipeline.
没有人可以把我的成果炸得稀巴烂
No one blows my tech to smithereens
还可以逃之夭夭
and gets away with it...
贝蒂·圣·苏西
美国陆军
除非她长这样
Unless she looks like that.
我不觉得她有意要伤害我
I don't think she meant to hurt me.
好吧 那她是个超能力者
Well, her being a meta-human
就解释了为什么艾灵将军对她有兴趣了
explains general Eiling's interest in her.
以及为什么他要把案件从我们手里抢走
And why he stole the case from us.
他不想任何人知道她的能力
He didn't want anyone to know what she could do.
-探长 -博士
- Detective. - Doctor.
所以 人肉炸弹
So... Human bomb.
看来中城的灾难日到了
Must be Tuesday in Central City.
是的 而且艾灵将军
Yes, and general Eiling's
也不是一个会轻易交出潜在财富的人
not one to give up a potential asset without a fight.
我们要赶在他之前找到她
We have to find her before he does.
巴里 我能和你说几句吗
Barry? Can I see you for a second?
你打算什么时候告诉我
When were you planning on telling me
艾瑞斯看到红色踪迹了
that Iris saw the streak?
我不是故意的 我无意中被她看到的
That was not planned. She caught me off guard.
我们约定过的
We had a deal.
你不让她知道超能力者的事
You keep her in the dark about the meta-humans,
我就不对你拳脚相向
and I don't go Floyd Mayweather on you.
好的 乔 我知道
Okay, Joe, I know.
而且她正在写一个博客
And she's writing a blog now.
我已经和她谈过这个问题了
I already talked to her about that.
那就再谈一次 再有说服力一点
Talk to her again. And be more convincing.
好的
Okay.
-你是说现在吗 -我就是这个意思
- You mean, right now? - Yes, I do.
好吧
All right.
你得停止再去写这个人的东西了
You've got to stop writing about this guy.
-他根本就不存在 -我看到他了 巴里
- He doesn't even exist. - I saw him, Barry.
他穿着红色套装 像是制服之类的
He wears a red suit, like, a uniform or something,
他的胸口上还有个闪电球
with a lighting bolt on his chest.
我的意思是 艾瑞斯 拜托
I mean, Iris, come on.
你昨晚在酒吧喝了酒
You were drinking last night at the bar.
我没醉 我知道我看见的是什么
I was not drunk, and I know what I saw.
他戴着一个面具
He wears a mask.
我觉得他还对我笑了
I think he smiled at me.
好吧 首先 如果他戴着面具
Okay, first of all, if he is wearing a mask,
也许说明了他不想人们知道他是谁
that probably means he doesn't want people to know who he is.
他是谁不重要
It doesn't matter who he is.
重要的是人们知道他的存在
What matters is that people know that he's out there.
你到底怎么了 这对我很重要
What is wrong with you? This is important to me.
你就不能支持一下吗
Why can't you be more supportive?
我只是 你还没把你的名字放上去
I'm just... you haven't even put your name on it.
一个匿名博客能有多认真啊
How serious can you be about an anonymous blog?
好吧 你知道吗 在我们一生中
Okay, you know what? Our entire lives,
你一直因为不可能的东西而激动不已
you couldn't scream loud enough that the impossible existed.
而如今真的发生在中城了
And now it's actually happening in Central City.
我也有证据证明 你就什么都不想知道了？
I have proof of it, and you don't want to know about it?
这说不通啊 巴里
That doesn't make sense, Barry.
所以当你恢复过去那个样子的时候
So when you're ready to tell me what this whole routine
我们再来谈
is really about, then we can talk.
怎么样
Yeah.
我们黑进了艾灵将军的监视设备
We've piggybacked onto general Eiling's own surveillance.
根据他们所说的
According to what they're saying,
发现可爱的圣苏西小姐在英格尔伍德
the lovely Ms. Sans Souci was just spotted in Inglewood.
哈罗德·哈德利医生办公室所在的社区
The same neighborhood as Dr. Harold Hadley's office,
对她进行过一些手术
the military surgeon who performed
的那个军医
several procedures on her.
这就是她在找那个文件夹的原因
That's why she was looking for the folder.
你一定要在艾灵之前找到她
You got to get to her before Eiling does.
好的
Okay.
哈罗德·哈德利医生诊所
-圣苏西中士 -你还记得我
- Sgt. Sans Souci. - You remember me.
很好 因为我记得你 医生
Good. Because I remember you, doctor.
我记得我从昏迷中醒来
I remember waking up from a coma.
你切开了我的身体
You started cutting me open.
我只是试图帮你舒缓病情
I was only trying to help ease your condition.
你控制不住
You couldn't control it.
你对我做了这个 你和艾灵
You did this to me. You and Eiling.
去把我的财富拿过来
Go bring me my asset.
你还好吗
You okay?
听我说 我能带你出去
Look, I can get you out of here.
我能帮你理解发生在你身上的事
I can help you understand what happened to you.
-怎么帮 -因为我也发生过
- How? - Because it happened to me too.
拜托了
Please.
目标已经走了
Target is gone.
当爆炸散布中城时
As the detonation dispersed throughout Central City.
有很多人都接触到包含
A number of people were exposed to a wave
难以估算的能量的爆炸波
of unquantifiable energy.
其中一个 就是你
One of those people... Was you.
十个月前你在中城
You were in Central City ten months ago.
我刚刚从阿富汗回来
I had just returned from Afghanistan.
我在那边拆除路边的炸弹
I was there defusing roadside bombs
然后 弹片炸入了我的身体
and... Shrapnel ripped through me.
我就被飞机送回美国
I was flown back state side.
花了几个月才基本恢复
Spent months at the base recuperating
我醒来后就发现
and next thing I know,
我成了那个几乎要了我的命的东西
I became the thing that almost killed me.
以及艾灵的最爱 实验室小白鼠
And Eiling's favorite, new lab rat.
暗物质肯定已经和你身体里
The dark matter must have combined
炸弹的微粒结合了在一起
with the bomb particulate inside your body.
我原以为是艾灵对我做的这些
I thought Eiling did this to me.
艾灵还没有聪明到能创造出一个像你这样的人
Eiling is not smart enough to create someone like you.
但是足够聪明到能看到你的价值
Clever enough to see your value.
你还知道有其他被改变的人吗
Do you know of any others who were changed?
是有一些
There've been a few.
但没人长得和你一样
But no one that looks like you.
对不起 那不太恰当了
I'm sorry. That was inappropriate.
请不要走
Please don't leave.
我知道怎么做前脑叶切断手术
I know how to perform a lobotomy.
我从没见过任何像她的细胞结构一样的东西
Her cellular structure's unlike anything I've ever seen.
她的氮水平打破了记录
Her nitrogen levels are off the charts.
你认为我们能帮她吗
Do you think we can help her?
回答这个问题之前 我们必须明白
To answer that question, we have to understand
她是如何运作的 而要理解那个
how she works, and to understand that,
首先我们必须在她的行动中研究她
first we have to study her in action.
你想让她炸些东西
You want her to blow stuff up.
-太好了 我们开始讨论了 -不是在这
- Yes, now we're talking. - Not in here.
-她还不稳定 -我知道
- She's too unstable. - I know.
我知道你知道
I know you know.
这是你现在的生活了 嗯
So this is your life now, huh?
测试像我这样的人
Testing people like me?
阻止像你这样的人
Stopping people like you.
和我曾经想过的不一样
It's not what I thought I'd be doing.
实际上 除了巴里
Actually, aside from Barry,
你是我们测试的第一个超能力者
you're the first meta-human that we've tested.
-超能力者 -只是一个称呼
- meta-human? - It's just a term.
哦 我的天 发生了什么
Oh, my God, what happened?
为什么你不说你被枪击了
Why didn't you say that you were shot?
只是擦伤
It just graze.
那里面有个东西
There's something in there.
一个追踪装置
A tracker.
锁住管道 带贝蒂离开这
Lock down the pipeline. Get Bette out of here.
我来应付艾灵
I'll take care of Eiling.
哈里森·韦尔斯 英雄竟何落得如此境地
Harrison Wells. How the mighty have fallen.
将军
General.
科技之星实验室
S.T.A.R. Labs.
这个地方曾经是那么的重要
This place used to be so important.
告诉我 当一个人经历
Tell me, what does one do
如此壮观的公开失败后会怎么做
after such a spectacular, public failure?
唯有适应 唯有发展
One adapts. One evolves.
他会下定决心扭转自己的命运
One becomes intent on reversing one's fortune.
你一直都是理想主义者
Always the idealist.
-你想要什么 韦德 - 我的财富在哪
- What do you want, Wade? - Where's my asset?
我不明白你在说什么
I have no idea what you're talking about.
我们跟踪她到这 哈里森
We tracked her here, Harrison.
在你看着你剩下的宝贵宫廷坍塌之前
Turn her over to me before you see the rest
把她移交给我
of your precious palace crumble.
哦 韦德 韦德 韦德
Oh, Wade, Wade, Wade.
我们原本可以改变世界 你和我
We could've changed the world, you and I.
427千帕
427 kPa's.
她的特劳茨尔等级在45左右
Her Trauzl rating is around 45.
和可塑炸弹一样
That's the same as any plastique.
可塑炸弹 哈 第一次就想到称号了
Plastique. Ha... first try!
你不是真的认真考虑过这个吧 对吗
Didn't really think this one through, did you?
在下段射程的时候 叛乱分子开始对车设置诡雷
Downrange, insurgents started booby trapping cars.
剩下的旅途中 我都很害怕
The rest of my tour, I was terrified
触摸到其他的车辆
to touch another vehicle.
如今 我剩下的人生都将在
Now, I'm gonna spend the rest
恐惧去触碰其他人
of my life terrified to touch another human being.
他们试图帮你了吗
Have they tried to help you?
是的 他们有帮助我学习如何去使用我的力量
Yeah, they've helped me learn how to use my powers.
而不是逆转它
Not reverse them.
如果他们能逆转它 你就不是一个超能力者了
If they could reverse it so you weren't a meta-human,
你愿意吗
would you?
一个朋友告诉我我有这样的速度是有原因的
A friend told me I was given my speed for a reason.
因为我是被选中的
That I was chosen.
我也不知道我是否相信它
I don't know if I believe that,
但我总想去帮助人们
but I always wanted to help people.
而现在我可以了
Now I can.
抱歉 嘿 乔
Sorry. Hey, Joe.
我看你和艾瑞斯的小谈话真是一个振奋人心的成功啊
I see your little conversation with Iris was a rousing success.
她刚刚发布了红色踪迹的另一个故事
She just posted another story about the streak.
中城里的红色踪迹
发布者：艾瑞斯·韦斯特
乔 我努力了 我真的努力了
Joe, I tried. I really tried.
她现在把她的名字放上去了 巴里
She's got her name on it now, Barry.
-什么 -乔
- What? - Joe...
是我的错 我不应该让你说任何事
It's my fault, I shouldn't have asked you to say anything.
我只是想你知道
I just wanted you to know.
好吗 再见
Okay? Bye.
有什么事吗
What was that about?
艾瑞斯又报道了红色踪迹
Iris posted about the streak again.
她签了自己的名字上去
She signed her name to it.
-噢 这不是什么好事 -对
- Oh, that's not good. - No.
如果我们正应付着的某一个
If one of these bad meta-humans
邪恶的超能力者知道她知道什么
we're dealing with figures she knows something...
他们也许会对付她 我知道
Then they may target her, I know.
抱歉 我们关门了
Sorry, we're closed.
哦我的天哪 是你
Oh, my God, it's you.
艾瑞斯·韦斯特
Iris West,
我听说你在写关于我的东西
I hear you've been writing about me.
你是真的
You are real.
我应该 额 让我理理我的头绪
I should, um... let me just clean up...
在屋顶上见我
Meet me on the roof.
我先和你说一声
I'll give you a head start.
我不希望你继续报道我的事
I need you to stop writing about me.
现在有很多人
There are a lot of people who need someone
都需要你这样的人
like you right now.
知道你的存在
To know that you're out there.
我有很多问题
I have so many questions.
你从哪里来
Where are you from?
我不能说
I can't say.
你是谁
Who are you?
我也不能说
I can't tell you that, either.
你怎么做到的
How can you do what you do?
你是个很差劲的记者
You're a terrible interview.
有很多东西都是你理解不了的
There's more to this than you can understand.
就请相信我
Just trust me, please.
我需要你停下
I need you to stop.
你能停下吗
Can you stop?
冲进大楼里 把人们救出来
Running into buildings and rescuing people
却不让人们知道你的存在？
without them even knowing that you're there?
我不是为了荣誉才这么做
I don't do this for the glory.
那是为了什么
So why do you?
听我说 我有一个朋友
Look, I have this friend,
在他很小的时候就发生了很悲惨的事
an he had something terrible happen to him when he was a kid.
他一直都在讲着
His whole life, he's been telling stories
那些不可思议的故事
about this impossible thing.
人们都嘲笑他 心理专家也分析过他
And people laughed at him. And shrinks analyzed him.
他一直都在寻找着一个解释
And he's been searching for an explanation ever since.
但现在 他似乎突然就失去了他的信仰
But now, suddenly, it's like he's lost his faith.
但你就是证明他不是疯子的理由
But you... you are proof that he wasn't crazy.
帮我救救我的朋友
Help me save my friend.
他很幸运
He's a lucky guy.
嘿 怎么了
Hey, what's wrong?
艾灵有发现你在那吗
Did Eiling find out you're here?
没有
No.
凯特琳正想要告诉我那个不是那么好的消息
Caitlin was about to give me the not-so-good news.
你体内的弹片
The shrapnel in your body
已经在细胞层面上和你融成一体了
has merged with you on a cellular level.
而用来剪切你DNA的技术
And the technology required to unsplice your DNA...
还没被发明出来
it hasn't been invented yet.
贝蒂
Bette.
没事 我知道了
It's okay. Roger that.
我只是需要一点时间 别担心
I just need a minute. Don't worry.
我确定我的眼泪不会炸掉什么
Pretty sure I can cry without blowing stuff up.
-现在怎么办 -让她加入我们
- What now? - She joins us.
-成为团队的一部分 -巴里
- Becomes a part of the team. - Barry...
你拥有不可思议的能力 可以帮助别人
You have an amazing ability to help people.
但她只能炸掉东西
She makes things explode.
她是第一个没有执意
She's the first meta-human not hell-bent
毁坏这座城市的超能力者
on destroying this city.
这样太危险了
It's too dangerous.
不能把她交给管道监狱啊
Well, she's not going in the pipeline.
我不是说要把她交给管道监狱
I'm not suggesting she go in the pipeline,
但她继续留在科技之星实验室
but were she to remain at S.T.A.R. Labs,
会让我们都陷入险境的
it would put all of us at risk.
什么险境 艾灵吗
From who? Eiling?
艾灵是个危险人物 巴里
Eiling is a dangerous man, Barry.
我们不想成为他的敌人
We do not want him as an enemy.
闪电球事件之后 如果你们没有找到我会怎样
After the lighting bolt, what if you hadn't found me?
我有可能就是她了
It could've been me.
追捕 逃亡 切断跟我认识在乎的所有人的联系
Hunted, on the run, cut off from everyone I know and care about.
是你们救了我
You guys saved me.
我跟你一样想要救她
And I want to save her just as bad as you do, Barry.
我们都想
We all do.
乔 你来这干什么
Joe. What are you doing here?
过来看看你妈妈案子的资料
Going over the materials in your mom's case.
你怎么样了
How's it going with you?
一级棒 我跟一个炸弹人交了朋友
Stellar... I made friends with a human bomb
我还承诺我能够帮她 但我帮不了
who I promised I could help, and then, I couldn't.
然后我终于知道艾瑞斯为什么要写红色踪迹的事了
And I finally diagnosed why Iris is writing about the streak.
她是为了我
She's doing it for me.
为了证明不可能事件是可能存在的
To prove the impossible is possible.
你怎么知道的
How do you know that?
红色踪迹可能跟她聊过了吧
The streak may have talked to her.
巴里 你觉得艾瑞斯会认不出你的声音吗
Barry, don't you think Iris would recognize your voice?
不会的 很酷的事情就是 我能
No, I can do this cool thing with my vocal cords,
震动我的声带 把声音变成这样
where I vibrate them so I sound like this.
我知道 这很酷 很酷
I know. It's cool, it's cool.
哇哦
Whoa.
既然你让事情进行到这个地步了 那么
Well, you put that out there now, so.
我要保证她的安全
I want to keep her safe.
你知道唯一一个能阻止她写下去的方法
You know the only real way to get her to stop
就是告诉她真相
is to tell her the truth.
伙计 你真的想要告诉她吗
Man, you really want to tell her.
-我什么都跟她说的
- I tell her everything. - Mm...
没有所有吧
Not everything.
有那么明显吗
Is it that obvious?
她没有察觉
Not to her.
但是 你知道多久了
But how long have you known for?
从你大到能知道爱是什么的时候
I have watched you be in love with Iris
我就看着你爱上艾瑞斯
since you were old enough to know what love is.
而且我等着你跟她表白已经等了好几年了
And I've been waiting years for you to tell her.
但是你没有
But you haven't.
我想是我动作太慢了
Guess I was too slow.
现在 她很幸福地跟别人在一起 所以
Now, she's happy and with someone else, so...
当上苍想要某事发生的时候
When the universe wants to make something happen,
不管是赐予一个年轻人光速
whether it be giving a young man lighting speed
或是让两个人在一起
or putting two people together,
它总是有办法让事情发生的
it has a way of figuring those things out.
我该回家了
And I got to get home.
谢谢
Thanks.
思科
Cisco?
他回家了
He went home.
我想我们思科对你有点一见钟情了
I think our Cisco's developing a little bit of a crush on you.
我已经不确定我该不该和人约会了
Not sure I'm prize winning date material anymore.
改变是难以接受的
Change is hard.
改变你的那场事故也让我坐在这轮椅上
The same accident that changed you put me in this chair.
抱歉 我不知道
Sorry. I didn't know.
我告诉你这故事不是为了博取同情
I don't share that story with you to garner sympathy.
我告诉你是为了阐述一个更大的要点
I tell it to you to illustrate a larger point.
什么要点
And what point is that?
我会不计一切去拿回我失去的一切
That I would do anything to get back what I lost.
-你也该如此 -我也会
- As would you. - I would.
我只是不知道要怎么做
I just don't know how.
你们士兵 管自己叫牧羊犬 我说的对吗
You soliders you call yourself sheepdog. Am I right?
快乐的过着普通的日子 直到有人攻击了我们的族群
Happy and normal until someone attacks our flock.
那天晚上被改变的每一个好人
Every good person who was changed that night,
像你这样的人 像巴里那样的人
people like you, people like Barry Allen,
这些人现在都是你的族群 贝蒂
those people are your flock now, Bette.
而艾灵将军绝不会停止攻击这个族群
And general Eiling will never stop attacking that flock,
而他总能达到他的目标
and he always gets his target.
除非你阻止他
Unless you stop him.
你清楚你的职责 中士
You know your duty, sergeant.
杀了艾灵
Kill Eiling.
这是最后的任务 然后你就能回家了
One last mission. And then you go home.
贝蒂在哪里
Where's Bette?
-她走了 -什么意思
- She left. - What do you mean?
-她去哪里了 -她没说
- Where did she go? - She didn't say.
那她还能去哪里
Well, where the hell could she be?
-快 快 -快 快
- Go, go! - Go, go!
听我指令
On me.
我准备好自首了
I'm ready to give myself up.
哦 我高度怀疑这一点
Oh, I highly doubt that.
你觉得你能往我身上扔一个吗
You think you can pull one over on me?
你不行的
You can't.
稍息 士兵
Stand down, soldier.
我监测到军队信号了
I got back on the military feed.
看来他们是去滨水区
Looks like they've gone to the waterfront
和贝蒂相会了
to rendezvous with Bette.
她要自首
She's turning herself in.
她不是自首
She's not turning herself in.
求你了上帝 希望他能赶得上
Please, let him get to her in time.
全世界的人都在谋划怎么摧毁我们的国家
All over the world, people are plotting to destroy our country.
结束我们的生命
To end our lives.
英勇的美国战士们可能会死于这场战场
Brave American soldiers are gonna die in that fight,
但是他们不必死
but they don't have to.
因为有你 我们就相当于有了胜利
Because of you, we could have victory.
我想要的 不过是想让这个世界变的更加安全
All I've ever wanted was to make the world a safer place.
最好的办法就是让你们从此消失
And it will be when you're not in it.
寻找掩体
Take cover!
你来这里做什么
What are you doing here?
作为一个战士并不意味着你可以滥杀无辜
Being a soldier doesn't mean you're a murderer.
快停手吧
Don't become one now.
对不起 我没看见他
I'm sorry. I didn't see him.
没关系 这不是你的错
Don't be. It's not your fault.
感谢你阻止了我
I'm glad you stopped me.
我会把你带回实验室
I'm gonna get you back to S.T.A.R. Labs.
巴里 韦尔斯博士他 他
Barry, Dr. Wells. He... he...
伙计们 有麻烦了
Guys, we have a problem.
贝蒂还好吗
Is Bette okay?
不 艾灵杀了他
No. Eiling killed her.
她在发光 她快爆炸了
She's glowing. She's gonna detonate.
天呐 照这样的体积和质量来算 爆炸将会是
Oh, my God, a mass that size, the explosion, it would be...
毁灭性的
Devastating.
巴里 你得赶快把她带出城区
Barry, you have to get her away from the city.
但是已经没时间了
But there's no time.
我能在水上跑吗
Can I run on water?
我只要加速到的一定程度就能冲上建筑物
I built up enough speed to run up a building.
那我需要多快的速度才能在水上跑
How fast do I need to go to run on water?
照你的体重来说
Assuming your weight...
450磅每步的重量
450 pounds of force per step for vertical suspension.
再加上水的阻力
Accounting for fluid drag.
大约需要每小时650英里的速度
Approximately 650 miles an hour.
你还必须跑出爆炸的范围 否则你也会死
You have to outrun the blast or you'll die too.
没有什么特别的事情
Nothing out of the ordinary occurred.
军队只是在
The military was simply conducting
做一项水下武器测试而已
an underwater weapons test.
大家不必惊慌
There is no need for panic or alarm.
中城十分安全 我向你们保证
Central City is safe. I guarantee you.
他当着我的面杀死了贝蒂
He murdered Bette right in front of me.
我们却什么都不能做
And there's nothing we can do to him.
有权利的人总是有办法免遭后果
Powerful men have a way of avoiding consequences.
-你会好的 -嗯
- You gonna be okay? - Yeah.
你可以在水上跑
You can walk on water.
你更算得上是个有趣的同事了
Puts you in pretty interesting company.
如果你是来洗衣服的 我已经放进去了
If you came to do laundry, I already have a load in.
不是 我是来跟你谈谈的
Uh, no. I-I came to talk.
我在办一个案子
I was working a case.
有一些人 我以为我们可以像朋友一样相处
Someone I really thought I could help befriend.
但是他们死了
But they died.
巴里 我很遗憾
Barry, I'm really sorry.
我虽然不是很了解她 但是我仍然感觉很难过
I didn't know her that well. But it still hurts.
就像我现在的感觉一样
And as bad as I feel right now,
我知道失去家人的感受
I know how much worse it is to lose someone who's family.
艾瑞斯 你现在写的这个东西 再冠上你的名字
Iris... Writing about this stuff, putting your name out there,
这很危险
it's dangerous.
所以我最后再请求你一次 停手吧
So I'm asking you one last time, please, stop.
我也最后一次问你
And I am asking you one last time
你到底怎么了
to tell me what is really going on with you.
为什么我们俩当中只有我一个人对这个感兴趣
Why am I the only one of us who's interested in this?
我想 这些跟我家庭有关的东西
I guess, just, all this stuff with my family,
我已经彻底放下了吧
I finally just put it behind me.
我希望你也能这样
I'm asking you to also.
也许这是我研究这个起因
That may have been how this started,
但现在对我来说已经不单单意味着这个了
but it's about something more than that for me now.
到底这个红色踪迹是谁 他从哪里来
Whoever this streak is, wherever he comes from,
不到全世界的人都相信他的存在 我是不会罢休的
I am not stopping until the rest of the world believes in him.
也许 我们这段时间不要再见面了
Maybe we shouldn't see each other for a while.
是的
Yeah.
再给我一杯苏打水 谢谢
Can I get another club soda, please?
嘿
Hey.
你们来这儿做什么
Hey, what are you guys doing here?
我觉得我们应该一起干一杯
We thought we should have a toast.
我喝酒不会醉的 记得吗
Doesn't work on me, remember?
巴里·艾伦 你应该是所有人中最
Barry Allen, you of all people
相信一切皆有可能的
should know that nothing is impossible.
我通过蒸馏 提纯出了高浓度酒精
I distilled a highly fermented, potent suspension.
差不多有500度
It's basically 500 proof.
我想今晚真要有人需要一醉方休的话 那一定是你了
I figured if anybody could use a drink tonight, it was you.
那么 敬贝蒂
So here's to Bette.
贝蒂
Bette.
哇哦
Whoa, oh.
这酒劲儿太快了
That hit too quick.
你晕吗
Are you buzzed?
嗯 有点儿
Yeah. Yeah, I'm buzzed for sure.
哇哦  真是个好东西
Whoa. Whoa, that is good stuff.
然后 就过酒劲了
And it's gone.
一步步来吧
Work in progress.
一个人之前问过我一个问题
For a guy who has experienced his fair share of mysteries,
我始终想不出答案
one mystery I still can't figure out
为什么有人进入我们的生活
is why some people come into our lives.
有人离开
Why some people go,
还有人成为你生活的一部分
and others become a part of you.
一些友谊感觉就像是会永远持续下去
Some friendships feel like they'll last forever.
-嗨 亲爱的 -嗨
- Hey, sweetheart. - Hey.
冰箱里有晚餐
There's dinner in the fridge.
谢谢
Okay, thanks.
艾瑞斯 你的博客
Iris, about your blog...
我不想谈这个 好吗
I don't want to talk about it, okay?
还有的友谊消失的很快
And others end far too soon.
不是所有的友谊都能持续一生
Not every friendship is meant to last a lifetime.
永远伴随一生的 是失去那个人的痛苦
What does last forever is the pain when that person is gone.
我想错你了 哈里森
I was wrong about you, Harrison.
你还是快我一步
You're still one step ahead.
对一个坐在轮椅上的人来说 这真不赖
Impressive for a man without the use of his legs.
恐怕我听不懂你的意思 韦德
I'm afraid I don't know what you're talking about, Wade.
一个可以通过用手触碰
A girl who can transform ordinary objects
就把一般物体变成爆炸物的女孩
into explosives with the touch of her hand.
今天我看见一个可以瞬间移动的男人
Today I saw a man who can move faster than the blink of an eye.
真令人惊讶
Extraordinary.
你的粒子加速器爆炸的那晚
The night your particle accelerator died
正是这些不可能事物出现的时候
was the night the impossible was born.
我觉得我们应该再次一起合作了 哈里森
I think we should start working together again, Harrison.
我觉得你应该走了
I think you should leave.
你知道的 我可以马上召集一支军队
You know, I can have a squadron of soldiers here
分分钟踏平这里
in minutes.
你知道的 我有很多新闻媒体在手
You know, I can have an army of press here like that.
相信我 将军 我非常乐意
Believe me, general, I'd be more than happy
验证一下
to testify to your involvement
你的行为是多么的不人道
in activities that were less than humane.
你再威胁我试试 我会终结你 将军
Threaten me again and I will end you general.
而我所说的可不仅仅是你的事业
And I am not talking about your career.
你知道么 我找出了你的小秘密 韦尔斯
You know, I figured out your little secret, Wells.
用不了多久 公众也都会知道
Won't be long before the public catches on as well.
我们一直努力就是想得到这个
This is everything we've been working to achieve.
我们是有同样的目标 将军 但是道不同不相为谋
We may have the same goals, general, but not the same means.
我不会让这项工程还没开始就结束的
I will not have this project end before it even begins.
只要他还在我的地盘
And as long as he's on my premises,
我不会让他再屈从于这种暴力了
I will not have him subjected to that kind of cruelty anymore.
我们不用说了
We're done.
没的说了 将军
We're done. General.
好走不送
Get out.
嘿
Hey.
没关系
It's okay.
没事儿的 小朋友
It's okay, boy.
没事儿了
It's okay.
他走了
He's gone.
别担心
Don't you worry.
我对你的未来另有打算
I have a whole different future in mind for you.
古鲁德